Correct. The answer is logarithm,
对 答案是对数
because logarithm has this very nice identity that says that the logarithm of
因为对数具有良好的特性
the product A times B is the sum of the logarithms of A and B.
即 log(ab) 等于 log(a) 和 log(b) 的总和
So this is what we do.
这就是我们要做的
We take our products and we take the logarithms,
我们得到乘积 使用对数
so now we get a sum of the logarithms of the factors.
现在得到因子对数的总和
So the ln(0.6*0.2*0.1*0.7) is equal to
所以 ln(0.6*0.2*0.1*0.7) 等于
ln(0.6) + ln(0.2) + ln(0.1) + ln(0.7) etc. Now from now until the end of class,
ln(0.6) 加 ln(0.2)  加 ln(0.1) 加 ln(0.7) 从现在开始到这节课结束
we'll be taking the natural logarithm which is base e instead of 10.
我们都要使用底数为 e 的对数 （自然对数） 而不是底数为 10 的对数
Nothing different happens with base 10.
底数为 10 的对数并没有太大区别
Everything works the same as everything gets scaled by the same factor.
所有原理都是相同的 它只是自然对数的结果乘上一个因子
So it's just more for convention.
这样做只是一种惯例
We can calculate those values and get minus 0.51, minus 1.61,
我们计算这些值得到 -0.51 -1.61
minus 0.23 etc. Notice that they are all negative numbers and that actually makes sense.
-0.23 等 注意这些都是负数 这也是符合实际的
This is because the logarithm of a number between 0 and 1 is always
这是因为 0 到 1 之间数字的对数都是负值
a negative number since the logarithm of one is zero.
因为对 1 取对数才能得到 0
So it actually makes sense to think of the negative of
所以 概率的对数都是负值 对它取相反数是行得通的
the logarithm of the probabilities and we'll get positive numbers.
这样会得到正数
So that's what we'll do. We'll take the negative of the logarithm of the probabilities.
这就是我们要做的 我们得到的概率的对数为负值
That sums up negatives of logarithms of the probabilities,
对它们的相反数进行求和
we'll call the cross entropy which is a very important concept in the class.
我们称之为交叉熵 这也是这节课中非常重要的概念
If we calculate the cross entropies,
如果我们计算交叉熵
we see that the bad model on left has a cross entropy 4.8 which is high.
我们看到左侧错误的模型的交叉熵是 4.8 这非常高
Whereas the good model on the right has a cross entropy of 1.2 which is low.
右侧的更优的模型交叉熵较低 是 1.2
This actually happens all the time.
实际上这是一个规律
A good model will give us
准确的模型可以让我们得到较低的交叉熵
a low cross entropy and a bad model will give us a high cross entropy.
而误差较大的模型得到的交叉熵较高
The reason for this is simply that
这纯粹因为
a good model gives us a high probability and the negative
好模型可以给我们较高的概率
of the logarithm of a large number is a small number and vice versa.
它的对数取相反数后是个较小的数字 反之亦然
This method is actually much more powerful than we think.
这种方法比我们想象的还要强大
If we calculate the probabilities and pair the points with the corresponding logarithms,
如果我们计算出概率 并且得到每个点所对应的对值
we actually get an error for each point.
我们实际上得到了每个点的误差
So again, here we have probabilities for both models and the products of them.
那么这里我们有两个模型的概率和概率的乘积
Now, we take the negative of the logarithms which gives us sum of
现在我们对每个对数取相反数并求和
logarithms and if we pair each logarithm with the point where it came from,
如果我们把每个对值放到对应的点上
we actually get a value for each point.
我们可以得到每个点的值
And if we calculate the values,
我们计算了这些值
we get this. Check it out.
就得到了这些东西 来看一下
If we look carefully at the values we can see that
如果我们仔细观察值
the points that are mis-classified has like
可以发现这些分类错误的点的值较大
values like 2.3 for this point or 1.6 one for this point,
如这个点是 2.3 另一个点是 1.6
whereas the points that are correctly classified have small values.
然而正确分类的点对应值都较小
And the reason for this is again is that
这个原因还是在于
a correctly classified point will have a probability that as close to 1,
分类正确点的概率更接近于 1
which when we take the negative of the logarithm,
如果对这个概率的对数取相反数
we'll get a small value.
就会得到较小的值
Thus we can think of the negatives of these logarithms as errors at each point.
因此我们可以把这些对数的相反数作为每个点的误差
Points that are correctly classified will have
分类正确点的误差较小
small errors and points that are mis-classified will have large errors.
而分类错误点的误差较大
And now we've concluded that our cross entropy will tell us if a model is good or bad.
现在我们得到结论 交叉熵可以告诉我们模型的好坏
So now our goal has changed from maximizing a probability to minimizing
所以现在我们的目标从最大化概率转变为最小化交叉熵
a cross entropy in order to get from the model in left to the model in the right.
从而使左侧模型转变为右侧模型
And that error function that we're looking for,
我们所寻找的误差函数
that was precisely the cross entropy.
就是这个交叉熵